chatforfree.org 2016-05-01

# Privacy Policy

Chatforfree.org has created this privacy statement & terms conditions in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this website: www.Chatforfree.org

Chatforfree.org does not sell, share or distribute any of the information that it collects with any business or persons not affiliated with it.

We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our Web site. Your IP address is used to gather broad demographic information. Our site's registration form requires users to give us contact information (like their name or user name and email address). The customer's contact information is used to contact the visitor when necessary and to reply to your email.

This site contains links to other sites. Chatforfree.org is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.

Our site uses a contact form for customers to request information, help and services. We collect visitor's contact information (like their email address) name and locations. Contact information from the registration and contact form is used to send orders and information about our company to our customers. The customer's contact information is also used to get in touch with the visitor when necessary.

Your Obligation

-This site enforces a strictly no nudity policy and you will be banned along with details provided to Law Enforcement in certain circumstances.

Data Collection

Chatforfree.org, as well as most sites on the Internet, uses "cookies" to enhance your experience on the web. Chatforfree.org cannot use these cookies to personally identify you in any way. This cookie can help Chatforfree.org ensure convenient features such as One session login, that are used to help the user navigate around the web site with more ease.

If you have any additional questions about Chatforfree.org's dedication to consumer privacy, please contact us.

Chatforfree.org does not sell, share or distribute any of the information that it collects with any business or persons not affiliated with it.

Public Forums

This site makes chat rooms, forums, message boards, and/or news groups available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information. Chatforfree.org is not responsible for the loss, misuse, or alteration of any personal information you disclose in public forums. Chatforfree.org is not responsible for interactions that happens between users through the chat room, discussion forum, both online and off-line. Chatforfree.org will never give out user information regardless of the situation unless obligated by law.

Security   
This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the personally identifiable information under our control.

The chat room is a public forum. Never give out your full name, address, telephone number, school name, or any other information that could actually identify you.

If you want to meet up with someone you met online, check their reputation with the Admins first .

Admins are there to help keep you safe in the room. If you ever feel uncomfortable for any reason, or don't know what to do, talk to an Admin or email us.

Chatforfree.org is not responsible for the loss, misuse, or alteration of any personal information you disclose in public forums. 

Chatforfree.org does not sell or share any of the information that it collects with any business not affiliated with it. 

Chatforfree.org is not responsible for interactions that happen between users either through the chat room and discussion forum, both online and off-line.

Chatforfree.org is not responsible for any webcams that has been streaming in our webcam chatroom. Chatforfree.org is a free webcam chatroom that allowing users to use their services for free and users must follows their rules of conduct. 

Contacting the Web Site   
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can fill in our [contact form.](http://contact.chatforfree.org/form-955181/Contact "contact")
